[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
I read the journal.
Everything about the exhibit.
Everything you've done
for me. Everything...
Everything I don't remember.
I read it all.
Kuya, I think she really regrets it.
She’s been here all day
waiting for you.
That's her choice, bro.
I'm just worried something
might trigger her.
I only did what I thought was right
and what was best for all of us.
Well, no.
And it's none of your business,
I don't need you because
this is my life!
It's you!
What? Me?
The crazy girl.
Estong, I need your help!
- Ma'am, can you try it imitating her?
- I don't know where Belle went.
I've been wanting to do this
to you for a long time.
What? Got something to say?!
Speak up!
You're really losing your mind!
Are you okay?
Don't you worry.
I'm here now, okay?
We're going to see Dr. Wanda.
- Stop it, stop the car!
- Belle. Belle!
Estong! Estong,
no! Estong!
Estong!
- Estong, stop the car!
- Belle!
Ricardo, I said let me
and my daughter out!
Mommy! Daddy...
Estong!
Estong, no! Estong!
Belle, sweetie? Belle!
- Sweetheart, what's happening?
- Belle?
Estong, I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
Everything that happened
to you was my fault.
- I'm so sorry!
- Sweetheart...
Sweetheart...nobody wanted
this to happen. It was an accident.
- None of it was your fault.
- Nang, it's all my fault!
It’s my fault. Why didn’t you
just report me?!
Why didn’t you just take me to the police?
Why?!
Sweetheart...
Estong is getting better now.
He's already recovering.
- Let's just wait for him to wake up.
- But what...what....what if he doesn't?!
What if suddenly something happens to him?!
What if he suddenly develops
complications, Nong?!
Sweetie, that's enough.
It's all my fault. Can't you see that?
No matter what I do, I'm not normal!
Something's wrong with me. I'm not normal!
Everything becomes complicated.
What should I do?
- I can't do this anymore!
- Belle...
I can't do this anymore...
no matter what I do.
That's...That's enough, Belle.
Please, enough.
I keep trying, right?
I keep trying to be normal...
but no, I'm cursed!
- We're all cursed!
- Sweetheart, no.
That's enough.
No, that's not true.
I'm tired, Nang.
Nong, I'm so, so tired.
I can't do this anymore.
- I'm so, so tired.
- Sweetie...that's enough.
That's enough, sweetie, please.
I can't do this anymore. I'm so tired.
- I don't want to be a burden anymore.
- Belle...sweetheart.
- Sweetheart, that's enough...
- Sweetie, come here.
- Sweetie?
- Belle?
Belle!
- Belle!
Sweetheart.
Belle?
Belle!
Doc...
is she okay?
Stable...
but I am worried.
It seems like the stress was too
much for her body.
That’s why I want to see how
she is when she wakes up.
Why, Doc?
We all know Belle's condition.
When she's going through
something difficult, her D.I.D. may react.
What kind of reaction?
There may be no changes.
But it's possible that
one personality may start
appearing more frequently,
or perhaps...
someone we haven't met
before may appear.
Doc...
there are others?
It's possible.
So I recommend that she undergo
an intensive, trauma-focused
treatment program.
That way, we can talk to
her more frequently...
monitor her more closely...
and help her
with whatever...
deep trauma she's carrying.
Belle, you don't have
to take all the blame.
It's also our fault.
But then again, it's true...
if she had accepted us back then,
Estong wouldn't have gotten hurt.
Tristan...
Children,
enough with the blaming.
What was meant to happen
has already happened.
What matters is...
we're all still alive.
Where’s my best friend, Estong?
I want us to play again.
Ah...
Yeye, Estong's still in the hospital.
He's still recovering.
Let's go!
Let's visit him.
Sure, but next time, okay?
Belle needs to rest too.
We'll visit him together.
Belle...
stay strong.
This is not the time to give up.
Yeah! Be strong, my play mate.
Please listen to us, dear.
Belle, how many times have I told you...
Yeah, listen.
Belle...
just keep on listening.
just calm down, okay?
Shut up!
- Ate Belle!
- Belle, why?
Shut up, all of you!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- What are you doing?
- Don’t do that, Belle.
- No!
Don't! Ate Belle, don't!
wait...
Hey, hey, hey, wait...
- Don't do it.
- Ate Belle.
- Please, just think about it carefully.
- No!
Belle, what have you done?!
Just like what I said to Estong...
you'll never see the outside world again.
Especially you, Ysa.
Belle!
Belle! Come back here, Belle!
I'm getting claustrophobic!
I cannot, like...
We won’t be able to go out anymore?
No, Yeye doesn't like that!
Belle, come on! I don't like this.
Belle?
Sweetheart?
Nang...
Sweetie?
Belle, are you okay?
Estong...
Where's Estong? I want to see him.
For you.
Thank you.
Wow!
- Wow, this looks delicious!
- Yeah, it looks good.
Hey, hey, hey, why— don't...
Don't eat that. That's for Estong.
But Pops, there are three of these.
And Kuya is asleep.
What? Is this supposed to go in his IV?
Ah...
- Come on, Pops. Let's eat this already.
- Alright, alright, uh...
- It might melt. I'll go ahead, okay?
- You go ahead, I'll follow later.
- The Pistachio is mine.
- No. Okay, then.
Uh...
Belle...
I just want you to know that...
this isn't your fault.
Okay?
Go on, go to him.
He really needs you.
Thank you.
They say talking can
help with the recovery.
But I don't know...
what to say to you.
Maybe just some memories?
But let's not talk about my memories.
Maybe just the memories
of my other personalities.
You know, I don't really like reading this.
I don't want to know what they did.
But if it'll help with your recovery...
I'll do it.
What do you want to talk about?
I'll just pick randomly.
Ysa's entry.
She said...
"Today was my first review
session with Estong
for his board exam in Accountacy."
Let's start. What...
do you mean by obligation to do
and obligation to deliver?
I feel like I have an obligation to
stay by your side so you don't fall asleep
while we study.
“He kept saying over and
over that he was struggling...”
“That he was confused...”
“But despite all that, I never once saw
or even heard him give up.”
"Estong isn't just determined
with his studies..."
"but with people, too."
"Especially with all of us."
"Every personality he met..."
"he wasn't afraid of,"
"and he didn't give up on."
"He went along with Cacai's antics..."
Yes! Oh my God, that's your angle!
There! Just like that.
Pose some more. There you go!
"He listened as Tristan
shared his sorrows..."
I just want to be happy.
You bring out the best of us.
"He played around with Yeye..."
- Wow!
- So pretty!
Yeye wants a medal!
Kuya Estong? Are we best friends now?
- Oh, sure!
- Pinky swear?
Pinky swear!
"He respected Lola Iska..."
Am I getting too heavy for you, dear?
You can stay there as long as you want.
You haven't properly greeted me yet.
"He bore the brunt of Bogart's temper..."
- Didn't I tell you to pose properly?!
- Wait, ow, ouch.
Bogart, no, no, no, no, no...
You might hurt yourself and the others.
"And even though we pushed him
away over and over..."
"he would always come back."
"Over and over..."
"not because he was stubborn,"
"but because he chose not
to give up on us."
"When we're apart, I watch
the videos of us together."
That's the person who helped us.
Woah!
Just...just relax, Bogart. Just relax.
You're my best friend, Yeye!
We're best friends now, Yeye. Okay?
No homo, bro. No homo...
Lola Iska!
Wake up, wake up.
Clo...clock it,
clock it...cloc...
Weighted Average Cost.
Computes an active
average cost per unit
based on total cost of goods available
divided by the total units.
Ysa...
thank you.
It's nothing.
And besides,
this is nothing compared
to what you did for me.
Well...
not just with this.
Thank you, because...
you all helped me change
the way I see myself.
Because honestly,
I was already about to give up.
And then you guys came along.
I felt like I was a blank canvas.
Nothing at all.
No direction.
All of you gave my life color.
Because of that...
I gave myself a chance.
Thank you...
because all of you never gave up on me.
I promise I'll be here for all of you..
always.
I won't give up on all of you either.
You know, I also used to think
you were just stubborn.
I also used to think you were
just being annoying.
But I was wrong.
You really made an effort
to get to know me.
Even after all the times
I pushed you away...
You know me?
You're the one who almost kissed me, right?
I said, don't follow me!
Why are you still here?
Aren't you leaving yet?
Lorenz and I are fine here.
But it’s still different when you
have someone to share your life with.
Someone who also has direction.
Unlike some people who just...
hang around while doing nothing.
Oh, you know what? That's true.
Even though I'm such a mess,
even though I'm so hard to deal with...
you didn't give up.
I'm here to ask you out, Belle.
And I'm serious about it!
You never left me.
- Please, stop. Please.
- Belle! Belle! That's enough!
- Huh? Huh?!
- Belle, that's enough.
Don't you worry.
I'm here now, okay?
Estong, you're not the one
who needs to disappear.
Hey, Alora.
- Which one did you say would suit me?
- This will do right? This will do.
So...
When...
are we gonna make it official, hmm?
You know? You're always such
a main character.
Have you even proposed yet?
And besides...
are we even an item?
What's our label?
You know what...
you're right.
We're basically just in a situationship.
It's because you got an attitude.
Wow... me? Really?
Look who's talking.
- We can't find Belle!
- Have you seen her?
We've been calling her all day, but
we haven't been able to reach her.
She hasn't gotten in touch with us.
What could've happened to her?
Maybe she got kidnapped.
Do you want me to call the police?
Maybe...
- maybe there's a new personality!
- Oh, I hope not!
- OMG!
- Aunties, you're not helping.
- Right. You're not.
- Wait a minute. Just wait, okay?
Everyone, just relax. Relax.
Just relax, okay?
Let's just relax.
- What?
- Love, just relax.
Relax. Just relax!
He seems relaxed.
- You guys look there!
- Alright, let's go to this side.
Come on, let's go!
- Let's go look for her over there.
- Belle?
Let's just relax! Let's just relax!
Just relax...
Relax.
Seriously? I can't even track Ate Belle.
Where are you?
What's the news, Capt.?
No one has seen her, sir.
We've already asked around
at almost all the terminals,
eateries, and stores around here.
Even in the neighboring barangays,
she's nowhere to be found.
- How about we call the police already?
- Yeah!
I already called them earlier.
So, what did they say, Kent?
They said Belle can't be considered missing
until 24 hours have passed.
How is she not a missing person?
We don't even know where she is.
That's just how the protocol works.
Ninong, Ate Belle's situation is different.
You know,
she doesn't have her medication with her,
or anything she can
use to calm herself down.
And we're not there with her.
What are we supposed to do?
Don't worry.
Even though she hasn't officially been
reported missing yet,
we can still help look for her.
Thank you so much, Cap.
- Thank you so much.
- Please help us.
My God, where is Belle?
What's happening to her?
- Wait. Maybe them. We can give these out.
- Okay, okay.
Mister, here.
Maybe you can help us
find her, if you know anything.
Mister...
Have you seen
her? She's missing.
Estong?
Son!
Oh, Kuya.
I thought I was going
to inherit Popsy's business.
What's wrong with you?
He ate all your Yogorino.
Pops.
Belle...
Where's Belle?
Anything there?
Nothing.
Kuya,
I'll go see Pops for a bit, okay? We
just need to sort out the discharge papers.
Alright.
It's Estong.
Estong!
- Tita Barbs, Tito Kent.
- How are you feeling?
We're so glad you're awake.
Yeah, Estong. Why did you call us?
Aren't you supposed to be resting?
Uh...
Can I talk to Belle?
Um...
Belle's missing.
How...how is she missing?
That's why we're here in her room,
looking for any clues that might help us
figure out where she went.
We've been looking for her all day.
We've already checked every place
she could possibly have gone.
But nothing. No luck.
Yeah. We're just waiting here for now
to see what happens.
Uh...I'll go look for Belle, Tita.
Oh, Estong, thank you, but...
we'll take care of it, okay?
What's important now is
that you get better.
Yeah, Estong, just get some rest.
You might strain yourself.
We'll handle things for now.
Uh...
Tita...
May I ask where
the house in Belle’s painting is located?
- House?
- Painting?
This one?
In Ysa's case, she has created
a world inside her mind.
Based on Ysa's description...
this looks like the house she grew up in.
Only safer.
You're seeing another woman!
Stop it!
What's wrong with you?
- No! We're leaving you!
- No... she's not coming with you!
- I'm taking her with me!
- She's staying here at home!
- I saw it! Just admit it!
- No!
You're not going to admit it?!
Ricardo, Iet me and my daughter out!
Mommy...
Let's play!
No! You're crazy!
Ysabelle is really sad,
so I'm keeping her company.
This is what you all wanted, right?
For all of us to be together?
Fine, then. I’ll give you exactly that!
I'm going to make sure that no one else
will get hurt because of us.
Especially Estong!
Belle...
Why are you staring at me?!
- Don't mess with me!
- Belle!
Belle...
It's her! She's the
crazy girl! It's really her!
Stop it! Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
You shameless prick! You bastard!
- Stop it.
- How could you do this to me!
I can't control them.
So many people are making
fun of me because of you!
- Estong, stop the car!
- Belle!
Estong!
Estong, no! Estong!
- What’s wrong with this?
- She tried everything already,
- but see? It’s still broken.
- Hello Mr. Bunny, hello Mr. Cheese!
- I should hit it like this. Tapping it won't work.
- Let's play?
No, we can’t. It’s still broken.
Hi Belle.
- Oh my.
- What was that?
- What happened?
- Yeye scared.
Who are you?
A new alter?
You had to add yourself to the mix, huh?
We’ve known each other for a long time.
I know everything you’ve been through.
You're here to help me?
Well, too late! Because,
I don't need you!
I'm not here to help you like they do.
Because you and I,
we want the same thing.
You know it deep inside, Belle.
What do you mean?
That's up to you.
I won't stop you.
I know how much we've been through.
You don't know anything.
You know nothing!
I know...
how it feels to be abandoned,
to be hurt...
I also know how it feels
to be consumed by regret.
It's hard to live in that situation.
And I know you already
know how this will end.
Do you want to end this?
I'm tired.
I’m tired of having to share
my life with them.
It's okay to be tired, Belle.
I understand where you're coming from.
What you’ve been through wasn't normal.
No one deserves a life like that.
I need someone who understands me.
Someone who knows what I need...
not what "we" need.
I understand you.
You need me.
Who are you, really?
You still haven’t told me.
Are you a new alter or not?
I'm not like them.
Like "them", who are ruining my life?
Like "them", who are protecting you.
- Bogart.
- Ysa.
Lola Iska.
Bogart...
Cacai...
Lola?
Lola.
Yeye.
Tristan.
They're all helping you.
But only I can give you the solution.
Belle...
I need to go to Belle.
I need to save Belle.
Belle!
That's why I'm here.
I am the release.
I can help set you free...
from everything that's been
troubling your mind.
All my life, I've been struggling.
I even feel like I can't take it anymore.
But I have no choice.
What can you do, right?
This is the life you were given,
but it’s not true that you have
no choice but to accept it.
Come.
Hold my hand.
Belle?
Belle!
If I go with you,
will everything be better?
Belle!
Belle? Belle!
Belle, wake up.
Belle? Belle?
Belle, don't!
What the hell?!
I don’t need any of you!
I don’t need you!
Belle, please. Don't listen to her.
Don't hear her out.
Who should I listen to?
You?
I'm tired of this life.
I'm tired of living a life
shared with all of you!
Belle, please.
That’s not going to make things better.
If I'm gone...
you'll all be gone too.
Our suffering and everyone
else’s will finally end.
We won’t be able to hurt anyone anymore.
You need to make a decision now.
Let's end this, Belle.
Belle...
Belle, Nanang and Nonong
are waiting for you...
along with everyone at Nagkaisang Bayan.
Belle...
Estong. Listen to Estong.
Estong's awake?
Belle?
Belle. Belle, wake up.
Belle...
Belle, the ambulance is coming.
Belle, don't leave me, please.
Belle!
Belle...
Belle, wake up. I'm here now, Belle.
Belle!
Ys...Ysabelle, please. Don't leave me.
All of you, please don't leave me.
Belle!
Belle, please!
Yeye, we're still going to play, right?
What do you want?
Do you want a lollipop?
Do you want some balloons?
I'll always be here if you want
someone to play with, okay?
Best friend.
Cai...
Cai, we're still going to have
our fashion show, right?
We'll pick out lots of clothes for you.
Please...Cacai!
Jestoni.
Tristan, um...
we're still going to karaoke, right?
Tristan, you said we'd sing together.
I haven't even heard you sing yet, please.
You said you'd make it up to me.
Bro.
Bogart...
Bogart, what do you want?
I can always be your punching bag.
It's fine by me.
Bogart, you can hit me
whenever you want.
Estong.
Lola...Lola Iska!
I'm sorry, I won't forget anymore.
I'll always greet you properly.
I'll always be respectful. I promise, Lola.
Lo...Lola!
My child.
Ysa...
I still don't know how to paint.
My paintings are still terrible.
I can't lose you.
Ysa!
Ysabelle.
Don't leave me!
Please! Wake up.
Belle...
Belle, I believe...
that everything can still be better.
I believe we can still be whole.
The decision is yours.
I'm just right here.
Belle!
Bro...
we're not here to steal your life from you.
We were created
because you could no longer
carry the pain alone.
We're here
to protect you from those
who would hurt you.
But you're the reason....
all of you are the reason
why I'm not normal!
Girl, no. How can you say that?
Trauma is the one to blame.
Not us.
In fact, we are your emergency
response and defense team.
What needs to end
is your belief that we're enemies.
As embarrassing as it is to say...
you're all my best friends.
We're not your enemies, dear.
We are not a curse.
We're the parts of you that have
been trying to love you...
in every way we can.
We love you, Ate Belle!
We love you, Belle.
Belle?
Estong.
Belle, I'm here now.
I'm right here.
Hey...
It's...It's Ate.
Estong.
It’s Belle.
Sweetheart.
Thank God, she made it home.
Ate?
Sweetie.
Ate.
I'm glad that you're okay now.
Thank you, Estong.
I hope we're going to be okay, too.
Hmm?
What do you mean?
Belle...
will you be my girlfriend?
Um...
Estong, it's not possible.
Why is it still not possible?
You should still go to Australia.
Then what? I'll just leave you behind?
You're not leaving me.
You'll achieve your dreams.
Belle, you're part of my dreams.
Estong, you helped me
achieve my dreams.
I want to support you, too.
I want to be here for you as
you pursue your dreams.
Even when I'm far away.
Belle, I'm not going.
I'm not leaving you.
I can't leave you.
Let me handle it, Estong.
It's enough for me to
know that you're there...
even when we're far apart.
Maybe this is also your chance...
to find out what you really want, right?
But don't worry.
I'll always be here for you.
You're right.
I know...
you can handle it,
and I can handle it as well.
Goodbye, Estong.
This isn't goodbye.
I'll be back.
I'll come back for you, okay?
I'll be waiting.
And now, let's welcome,
the woman of the hour...
the artist of these masterpieces...
Ms. Ysabelle Navarro.
- Congratulations!
- Congrats, Belle!
Congratulations, Belle!
At first, I thought...
I had to choose who I really was.
I thought...
there were things that had to be gone
for me to become whole.
But I was wrong.
All of them...
are part of who I am today.
Every fear
that I faced,
every wound I endured,
every version of myself
I tried to forget...
All of that, all of them, are a part of me.
This journey wasn't easy,
but I learned...
that you don't have to
erase any part of yourself
in order to love yourself.
Now...
I'm embracing them.
Now, I have accepted them.
Yahoo!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations, everyone!
The event was successful.
I'm really gonna be famous!
I told you,
Belle could do it!
And so could all of us. See?
We were able to do it
because we all came together.
Thank you, Ysa.
You looked after all of us.
Thank Belle, too...
for letting us be a part of her.
You know,
I'm so proud of all of you,
my dear children.
There was a reason
why we were created,
and I'm glad
that we came together
and finally got along.
Now that we've become one...
we're whole,
together.
- Congrats, Belle.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Hmm...
So, is it official now?
It's been two months, Ate.
Hey, it's been three months.
Oh, right.
Okay then, lovebirds. Congrats!
Well, even bigger
congratulations to you, Ate.
This is such a huge success.
Thank you, Jayden.
Too bad Nong and Nang
aren't here anymore.
Yeah, they went home early.
They must've gotten tired,
but they said they'll make it up to us
at the blowout tomorrow.
I'm sure this won't be the last one, Ate.
So many people are praising it.
Hmm...
I don't want to think about that yet.
Maybe I should just take
a break for now.
Oh!
Perfect timing.
All you want is a break, Ate?
Well,
maybe this is it.
Hot Americano,
without sugar, ma'am.
Estong.
Hi, Belle.
Congratulations.
When did you get here?
A while ago.
Now...
Now, I have accepted them.
I saw everything.
Surprise.
Looks like it wasn't a break that came,
but fate.
Just like us.
Just like us?
- We're sweeter than them, right?
- Yeah.
Right? Come on, say it.
Give me a kiss.
- Not here.
- Not here?
Hey, I know this. I remember this.
Estongville, right?
It's amazing, right?
It's been years,
but it feels like it was only yesterday.
You know, Estong...
Back then, whenever
a new personality came out...
I got scared.
It's like...
I didn't know myself anymore.
I thought that,
aside from my family and friends...
there would never be a special man
who could accept me and
love me completely.
But when I met you...
turns out, it was true.
There's someone.
Thank you, Estong.
I've proven to myself that
it's enough to have just one person...
who never leaves you,
who's always by your side,
loves you,
and accepts you completely,
along with every version of yourself.
As for me...
well...
When I was in Australia,
I thought I had to go
far away to figure out
what I really wanted in life.
But the farther away I got...
the more I saw you in my plans.
I realized that...
I never needed to fix you,
because there's nothing
wrong with you, Belle.
I just needed to be enough
for you.
I just needed to work on myself.
Looks like you've worked things out, right?
There's one more thing I realized.
My direction.
The direction I'm really heading in,
because...
no matter where I go,
I know I'll always find my way back to you.
I thought I had to find where I'd be happy,
even though
deep down, I always knew...
that I'm happiest when I'm with you.
I love you, Ysabelle.
Estong...
I love you lots.
- Ew! Yucks!
- Yeah!
Ew!
Oh, Lola!
Look at Lola, she's so happy.
You said...
"Love you lots."
So you should...
kiss me lots, too.
Mmm... I already said "I love you lots."
No "kiss me lots?" Come on.
MkvDrama.net